Now I am on the Shinkansen
What a great name!
Ringo
Hello everyone!
I'm a little embarrassed because I'm all alone.
I don't speak loudly
I'm on the Shinkansen right now.
It's been a while since I've been off work today
I'm going to visit my grandma's house
I'm on my way to Fukushima
I'm not going to
me
I'm here.
I've arrived at Fukushima!
It's a little cold.
You look cute.
What?
They're picking us up at the station, so we'd better hurry.
Is there a Mr. Dedicated Main from Fukushima?
Can we meet him?
There's another Mr. Dedicated Main today.
It's not by chance, is it?
Where am I?
Inside? Inside?
Oh, my God.
What is this?
What am I going to do?
I'm trying to get rid of the trash. Is there any trash?
I'm just wondering if you have a dumpster. It's the west exit.
Oh, there's a trash can.
I have a package.
I'm kind of standing out.
Maybe I'm very conspicuous.
West exit.
This is the west exit.
All of them are in suits.
I'm the only one dressed like this.
It's been a while!
Camera!
You're doing it?
You're taking pictures of yourself!
Oh, my God!
Long time no see!
How are you?
I'm good. I'm good.
What's going on? Where did you put this?
I wasn't feeling well.
You weren't well?
It's too windy. I'm a little restless for once.
I'm fine.
It's windy.
No, I'm not calm either.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Slippers.
I don't need slippers.
Why not?
I'm fine.
I'm wearing socks.
Yeah. - Yeah.
You don't like it. I don't wear slippers.
You're not wearing slippers?
No, they're dangerous.
Really?
Well, I can get them myself if you need them.
Okay.
No, it's okay.
It's dangerous.
Just in case.
Thank you.
What was that? What's with the construction?
No, sir.
Which ones can I wear? This one.
Take them down. Can I wear them with you?
They're pretty.
Is it?
Yeah, they're cute.
This one's cute.
You haven't changed at all? Just here?
Yeah.
Why is there a Merry Christmas?
It's Christmas in 2012.
It's Christmas.
Yeah, I guess it is.
Where do I put my luggage?
Oh, luggage?
Uh-huh.
Can I take this once?
Yeah. - Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
They moved the stairs out here, so it's a little bit more gradual, 'cause the aunts were coming in here, and it was steep.
It's really, really nostalgic. I remember it so well. Remember? I think it's got a picture on it. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I remember. Okay.
Here we go.
This is almost... oh, this is now.
Uh-huh.
There's the...
The study?
He's mostly there.
What's he doing?
I'm on the computer.
You can use a computer?
Yeah, I can.
Wow.
I get hotels and stuff on the computer.
Oh, I see.
You can sit there.
You can use the bathroom or...
You can put your luggage...
Oh, I can put it there myself.
That's why I didn't get it.
Yeah, great name.
So, Dad didn't explain it to you.
But I knew what it meant.
It's like, so that people can smell the fragrance of compassion.
I heard "person" means something like caring, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, to be a person who can smell the fragrance of compassion.
But I don't know this one.
This is, you know, the so-called flower...
Ohana, in the Shamisen style...
Tade-ryu... it's called tade...
It's a kind of plant.
And the Tade school...
The...
Tade-ryu...
So they give each one of us a name like this.
Shamisen...
Yes, yes...
So, the master, or...
What do you call it...
When you get certified...
And this is...
It's named after my master.
He named all of his apprentices after this flower.
He chose this name himself.
It means "one flower" and you took this from here, right?
That's why it's like this.
Maybe you were wondering why it came like this. Maybe that's why she admired her so much.
He said, "Yeah, she's great.
And when she said "Shamis," he said, "Hitka," which is a nice name.
She thought it would be a good name for her daughter when she was born. She never mentioned it to me.
She never told me... and she didn't care for it... so I thought, well...
I don't know about this...
I had heard that my late grandma got this from the head of the maintenance department, but I guess I forgot about it, even though it was there.
She used to come into this room a lot, and she loved it, because she would come in and say hello to her grandmother.
Oh, yeah, that's great. She said it was great.
She's the one who praised you.
Wow.
Is this Grandma's?
What was her name?
Me?
Yes, it is.
Wait a minute.
It's cute.
I'm trying.
Is it great? This is.
But it's cute.
It's cute.
It's like it hasn't been dyed yet.
When you were celebrating your grandmother's birthday...
You painted something, didn't you?
You're not very good at it.
You're good in your own way.
I worked really hard on it.
Yes, I did.
I'm sure it made him happy.
I'm sure he was happy.
When you were celebrating your grandmother's birthday.
That's right.
I used to look at her like this all the time.
What? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
What's bad?
When do you say "bad"? When you're happy?
Oh, my God.
No, I don't think so.
When you say "great"?
What's bad is when I say it's bad.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
You might use that when it's bad.
That's right.
Do you want the lights on?
No, I'm fine without the lights on.
Why don't you turn on the light?
What?
You remember that, don't you?
I remember.
I used to love this dress.
It's so cute.
It was neat.
Yeah, it was neat.
I used to send pretty or neat things to people.
I used to send them to people.
But then I didn't know what she liked.
I didn't know what she liked, so I stopped.
Difficult girl.
It's not what I like.
That's it.
My mom's.
I don't know right away.
I'll make you some coffee.
That's fine.
I'll see you later.
It's my only day off.
That's great.
Oh, man.
Wait a minute. I'm in trouble.
Oh, my God.
It's so round.
Look at this one.
It's too round.
Papa, you're so handsome.
Oh, my God.
Really?
Kindergarten.
Oh!
Oh.
That's my sister and this is me.
Japanese-style room.
Oh, that's me.
Isn't she cute?
It's cute.
You're cute.
You were cute.
Stop saying I was cute.
Like you're not cute now.
You're an adult now.
You're beautiful now.
That's what you call beautiful.
A little girl that young, a little girl, she's beautiful.
They laugh at me.
Cute
She's pretty.
No, they're not.
I'll look at it.
Here we go.
Well, you know, we're all here with our crews and stuff, and we're still taking pictures of our crews and stuff.
We go on location a lot, don't we?
Even on location. I mean, how did you move around? On location.
We had to run inside the bus or else we'd be surrounded by fans.
So when the shoot was over, I'd run.
And then we'd run inside the bus, and everyone would surround the bus with bars.
It's more than that now, it's an exaggeration, so, in that sense, there's no other way.
There's no other way.
So you played a child actor because your father was a producer in the East?
In short, there weren't many child actors.
But when they said they had to use kids...
But when they talked about having to use kids, my dad was like, "You're in!
He said, "Well, you're pretty good at it.
And that's how he became famous at the time.
Ajari in Kyoto, my favorite place.
Ajari.
Let's try it.
I'm having coffee.
I have a cousin.
I used to love this guy.
You've met him, right?
I think we might have met.
I've met him... at a celebration.
This is...
It's a sweet from a place in Aizu called Tarouan.
There's something in the middle.
A rice cake in the middle?
No, it's like a cake.
There's a chocolate filling.
Oh, like it's spilling.
Let's do this.
Your mom's a doctor.
And your father is a businessman.
He's from Okinawa.
That's why he has Okinawan blood.
I have Okinawan blood too?
Yes, that's why.
I see.
A little.
That's why you see, Yochiya's mother is Fujikichi.
She was born and raised in Tokyo, Japan... and went to the Toho Medical University... there.
Toho Medical University... and qualified as a doctor.
Doctors of that era were amazing. Amazing.
It's like we're all still living in the same dormitory. My friends from back then stayed close.
We stayed in touch until he passed away.
huh?
I'm getting sleepy.
People channel.
When the fruit gets too full, it gets too small.
That's how people get them.
Oh, my gosh! That's so cute!
That's a first! That could be a real first! It's an apple.
It's so cute!
Super cute!
We have apples, too.
A dog?
There's a dog.
Whose dog?
I have a bad cold.
Looks good. I like it.
I want an apple.
Let's take a picture.
I'll take a picture when the cold stops.
It won't stop.
It's just stopped for a minute now.
Can we go inside?
I don't know what kind of apple this is right now.
It's an apple.
It's an apple that belonged to a friend of my grandma's.
It's the prettiest apple I've ever seen.
She said I could have it because it's my grandma's friend's.
You don't want Grandma's?
No, it's okay.
It's nice to have a puppy.
There's a puppy.
He's over there in the shed.
Hey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's why I'm here, Iceman.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Walking?
Hmm? Car? No, by car.
Oh, by car. It's the wrong side of the road.
Oh, wrong road? I'm taking the car.
I'm just a little bit...
It's a little dirty. Are you okay? Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
I might leave it somewhere else.
There we go.
Didn't we leave the nylon bags in the car?
But you know what? It's not dirty. It's clean.
Ta-da!
What's that, what's that, what's that?
The yellow one is Olin.
Green?
Yellow? Green? Yellow?
Olin.
And one more thing.
"Olin.
Oh, it's written...
Gunma Maigetsu?
It's so cute!
How delicious is Gunma Maigetsu?
What's this?
It's so red!
It's got nectar. It's so cute!
What was it?
Bees?
The bees are coming out.
Did you guys know that?
Did you guys know that bees are the reason we have apples?
Did you know that?
Did you know there was a bee?
I didn't know that.
It's the first time I've heard of it.
I didn't know bees could do such good things.
I thought bees were dangerous.
Butterflies do it too.
Butterflies make some of the fruit?
Butterflies?
Bees.
Bees?
Bees. They hire bees.
They have a bee company.
Beekeeping.
Beekeeping Division?
Beekeeping?
That's great.
They're all over the country.
We'll eat apples when we get back to the hotel.
Fukushima has delicious fruits.
Peaches? Peaches? Peach tree?
How do you know it's a peach tree? That's amazing.
That's great.
It's called a fruit line.
There's a fruit line all along this road.
They have a fruit line in Yamanashi, too.
Yeah.
Cherry blossoms turn red?
Cherry trees turn red?
What?
What? Wait a minute.
Do all trees turn red?
Some don't.
Deciduous trees do.
Deciduous trees.
Water-leaved trees, like pines.
Oh, waterleaf trees.
They don't change their leaves.
Evergreen trees always have leaves.
They have leaves in the winter.
These don't all lose their leaves.
New-leaf trees are evergreen, and they always have green leaves.
They are called deciduous trees, and they lose their leaves.
What about the red-leaf trees?
They have broad leaves.
I make bonfires, so I always use both new-leaf trees and red-leaf trees.
Wow.
That's great.
It's fresh, when people come over.
And the ones that don't.
That's right.
I'd like to see it become a little more natural.
Yeah.
And no insects.
Cackle, cackle, cackle.
I don't mind dogs.
I have a dog.
No dogs.
Animals are fine.
But not insects.
I love insects.
Because, Dad...
I mean, you know...
He had, like, a hundred beetles in the house.
That's amazing.
I've loved them since I was little.
You're good.
When he had them at home, I really wanted him to stop.
I really did.
You can see the mountains on the right there, and there's a little bit of smoke.
What? What?
The smoke?
It's a transfer.
That's all bad.
Everything's bad.
One.
Kill.
Yeah.
Sutra.
That's all bad.
I'm gonna be so smart with you two.
Yeah, you're right.
To the left is Azumako Fuji.
Azumako Fuji.
Fuji.
All of the eruptions in Calterra are shaped like that.
Fuji is a typical example.
There are volcanoes all over Japan.
They are all shaped like that.
Fuji's smaller shape.
Fuji, because it is not as big as Mt.
There are small Mt.
Fuji.
What's the name of the mountain near Yatsugatake, what's it called, Akadake?
Akadake.
Kurodake?
No.
Kitadake?
Yes, but...
Akadake and Kitadake?
Kitadake is the highest mountain in Japan, in the Southern Alps.
Kitadake?
That's right.
Second only to Mt Fuji.
Kitadake after Mt Fuji?
That's right.
I didn't know that.
I've never heard of it.
That's right.
You see this Yatsugatake mountain here?
Yes, yes, I see it.
The one on the right is Mt. Kaikomagatake.
It's Mt...
You know it?
You know it, right? That's...
What? I don't know.
Don't climb the Yatsugatake.
I climb a lot, Dad.
Yatsugatake.
You're very active, aren't you?
He climbs mountains and rides his bike.
Yes, active.
He's grown up since he was a little kid. He's a natural.
I'm just starting to get used to it.
I remember your voice cart.
When you talk to me, you circle around me.
Just like Leo, you know, going in circles around me.
Why don't you sit in one place?
My eyes are dizzy.
I'm jumping out of my skin.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.